Audrey Bodine

Springfield, Missouri (417) 771–1303 audreyebodine@protonmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/audrey-bodine https://github.com/Audrey-Bodine

INTRODUCTION

Currently building my website design portfolio with a focus on front-end development. Experienced in entrepreneurial pursuits, I am familiar with creating graphic designs to meet client specifications. During my undergraduate studies, I developed skills in analytical and creative thinking. I am comfortable working and researching independently as well as collaborating in group settings. I excel at communication, particularly in coordinating and managing team objectives.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science - Information Technology/Application Development

Missouri State University

GPA (Combined Cumulative): 3.85

August 2021 - May 2023

Springfield, Missouri

The Honor Society of Phi Kappa Phi, Golden Key International Honour Society, Dean's List

Associate of Arts - Business

Ozarks Technical Community College

GPA: 4.0

Springfield, Missouri

Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society, Chancellor's List

WORK EXPERIENCE

Social Media Content Manager

Self-employed, @audrey.bo.author

February 2018 - Present

Remote

- Produces photos for theme consistency
- Utilizes software for graphic design
- Engages with audience through captions and comments

Graphic Designer

June 2020 - September 2020

Innovia Group LLC Freelance

- Adapted concept ideas into digital artwork
- Created infographics to meet client's needs
- Utilized software to format designs

Website Content Editor October 2019

Innovia Group LLC

Freelance

- Researched company website to produce content aligning with mission statement
- Recommended select written content revisions
- · Delivered more edits than client expected, on a quick turnaround time

Online Marketplace Seller

2016 - 2019

Freelance

Self-employed, Etsy

- Produced greeting cards and digital downloads
- Interacted with clients to design custom artwork
- Created product photos for listings

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- · Social media content creation
- English grammar and punctuation

- Miro
- Visual Studio Code
- Mac OS
- Procreate
- Affinity Suite

RELEVANT COURSES

- Technical Writing
- Intro to Java Programming
- Intro to .Net Development w/C#
- Database Management Systems Concept and Design
- Database Application Development with Oracle

SOFT SKILLS

- Communication
- Organization
- Creativity
- Perseverance
- · Critical thinking
- Collaboration
- Positivity